Register of the Poland. Poselstwo (Czechoslovakia) Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- SERIES NO. XIII. PRESS AND PUBLICATIONS
  - C/Other
    - c/Publications on federation
      - 1943
        - Central European Federation (Folder 14: 8)
      - 1944 - Czechoslovak Newsletter
        - January-June (Folder 14: 9)
        - July-December (Folder 14: 10)
    - d/Soviet press on Czechoslovakia
      - 1942 (Folder 14: 11)
      - 1943 (Folder 14: 12)
    - e/Non-involved countries on Poland and Czechoslovakia
      - 1943 (Folder 14: 13)
      - 1944
        - Hungary (Folder 14: 14)
        - Lithuania (Folder 14: 15)
      - 1945 - Sweden (Folder 14: 16)
- SERIES NO. XIV. SPECIAL DOSSIERS
  - A/Slovakia
    - 1943 (Folder 14: 17)
    - 1944 (Folder 14: 18)
    - 1945 (Folder 14: 19)
  - C/Main acts on Polish-Czechoslovak cooperation (Box 15)
    - General. List of acts (Folder 15: 1)
    - 1940 (Folder 15: 2)
    - 1941 (Folder 15: 3)
    - 1942 (Folder 15: 4)
    - 1943
      - General
        - March (Folder 15: 5)
        - May (Folder 15: 6)
        - June-September (Folder 15: 7)
      - Czechoslovak-Soviet agreements (Folder 15: 8)
    - 1945
      - General (Folder 15: 9)
      - Yalta Conference (Folder 15: 10)
  - D/Balkan states and Danube Basin
    - 1943
      - General (Folder 15: 11)
      - Austria (Folder 15: 12)
      - Bulgaria (Folder 15: 13)
      - Hungary (Folder 15: 14)
    - 1944 (Folder 15: 15)
  - E/Slask Cieszynski (Teschen Silesia)
    - 1920 - Paris Peace Conference
      - General (Folder 15: 16)
      - Czechoslovak documents (Folder 15: 17)
    - 1938 (Folder 15: 18)
    - 1942 (Box 16)
      - General (Folder 16: 1)
      - Slask Cieszynski, 1918-1921: Zbior Tekstow Informacyjnych i Dokumentacyjnych Ulozony na Podstawie Materialow Archiwalnych Ambasady R.P. w Londynie
        - Part I (Folder 16: 2)
        - Part II (Folder 16: 3)
      - Sprawy Slaska Cieszynskiego Biuletyn, Nos. 2-5 (Folder 16: 4)
      - Zagadnienia Slaska Cieszynskiego, by Franciszek Bajorek (Folder 16: 5)
    - 1943
      - General
        - General (Folder 16: 6)
        - List of materials on Slask Cieszynski (Folder 16: 7)
      - Parliamentary Debates: House of Commons (Folder 16: 8)
      - Sprawy Slaska Cieszynskiego Biuletyn, No. 6 (Folder 16: 9)
    - 1944 (Folder 16: 10)
  - F/Soviet-Czechoslovak relations
    - 1944
      - General (Folder 16: 11)
      - Panslavic movement (Folder 16: 12)
    - 1945 (Folder 16: 13)
  - G/Subcarpathian Ukraine, 1945 (Folder 16: 14)